#### SAM TAHMASBI

Ottawa, Ontario samantahmasbii@gmail.com +15149925101

#### **SUMMARY**

Combine a building engineer background and a master's degree in architecture with extensive experience in customer service. Known as a hard worker who willingly takes additional responsibility while juggling multiple projects. Expert in architecture, design, development, customer service and excellent computer skills.

### **CORE QUALIFICATIONS**

• Excellent computer skills • Design Consulting • Client Relations • Excellent photography skills • Knowledge of building code • excellent communication skills • Ability to work in a team • Comfortable working in a fast-paced environment. • Exceptional drafting skills • Development and organization of CAD libraries and projects • Proficiency in engineering concepts • Problem-solving • Detail-oriented • Team building • detail-oriented • Good knowledge of vehicles and mechanical industry • Excellent mathematical and statistical skills

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: • CSS • HTML • JavaScript • JQuery • Python

<u>DESIGNING TOOLS:</u> • Wordpress • Bootstrap • 3dsMax • Revit • AutoCAD • Photoshop • 20\20 design •

ArchiCAD

MS OFFICE: • Microsoft Excel • Microsoft Word • Powerpoint

### **EXPERIENCE**

Drafter. CAD designer. Özyurtlar Insaat Construction Company Turkey. Jul 2014 to Aug 2017 Responsibilities:

- Planned, designed, and furnished residential properties to create unique living spaces.
- Developed 3d and 2d projects with Autocad and Revit
- · Produced drawings and layouts assisted the clients throughout the projects
- Estimated costs and materials
- Worked with project manager and engineers to communicate, problem solved and updated models for coordination and design issues
- Followed changes in industry trends and changing styles.
- Followed engineering content standards and development procedures
- · Received instruction on daily work and general instructions on new assignments
- · Created 3D models and rendering
- Developed and prepare design sketches
- Scheduled and attended site visits to measure and photograph spaces, and review and approve information and installations.

## **ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Web Developer

Feb 2018 to present Globit-Germany. Remotely

Branch Manager Nazeran Exchange - Toronto, ON Sep 2018 to April 2019

# **EDUCATION**

A graduate certificate in web development

Aug 2017 to Jul 2018. Concordia University

Computer-Aided Design (CAD)

Aug 2017 to Jul 2018. Concordia University

Master's degree in architecture

Sep 2012 to Jun 2014.

National Aviation University

Bachelor's degree in Civil engineering

Sep 2006 to Jun 2010.

National Aviation University

Diploma in Computer Science (Post-secondary diploma)

2005 to 2006. European University

Licences: G Driving License. Clean driving record